https://delawarehumane.org/privacy-policy/

701 A St Wilmington DE 19801
(302) 571-0111
info@delawarehumane.org
Support DHA!
|
Privacy PolicyHome Privacy Policy
Delaware Humane Association (DHA) has created this Privacy Policy to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your personal privacy within our website. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website located at delawarehumane.org and dehumane.org. In order to fully understand your rights we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy.
DHA values your privacy. To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, this Privacy Policy notifies you of the following:
What personally identifiable information of yours is collected through our website;
Who collects such information;
How such information is used;
With whom your information may be shared;
What choices you have regarding collection, use and distribution of your information;
What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control;
How you can correct any inaccuracies in your information.
Questions regarding this statement should be directed to DHA by sending an email to jhayes@delawarehumane.org. Please reference this Privacy Policy in your subject line.
For our Donor Privacy Policy, click here.
What Information We Collect and How We Use That Information
Our mailing list subscription, contact, registration and donation forms require users to give us contact information that may include name, email address, format preference (HTML vs. text), address, interests, and similar information. We know that many of our visitors and site users have ongoing concerns about their addresses or other personal information being sold to or shared with third parties. Please be assured that we do not and will not share, sell or rent anyone’s information with other organizations or individuals. We do not request or store sensitive information such as credit card or social security numbers from our website visitors unless payment for a donation or registration for an event is required. Please see “Financial Transactions” below for more information.
Internet Protocol Address
We collect an IP address from all visitors to our website. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our website, analyze trends, track users’ movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the site, and deliver customized, personalized content. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Use of “Cookies”
Our website may use cookies to enhance your experience while using our website. Cookies are pieces of information that some websites transfer to the computer that is browsing that website and are used for record-keeping purposes at many websites. Use of cookies makes web surfing easier by performing certain functions such as saving your passwords, your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular website and to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard.
Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our website will not function properly when you view them.
Financial Transactions
To process donations and registration payments for events and classes, it is necessary to provide DHA with your credit card information for processing and billing. Your information is collected and transferred over the Internet securely. The credit card information that you provide to us is used only for the transaction(s) you request and will not be used for any other purpose. We use a cloud-based service from Bloomerang to allow us to manage and process all transactions and associated data. Please view Bloomerang’s Security Policy for further information.
Security
All information provided to DHA through our website is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us, making your connection to our website secure. Our SSL certificate is served through and verified by GoDaddy.com, Inc. (learn how). However, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.
Other Websites
Our website contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website for which DHA has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such sites as their policies may be different than ours.
Changes to Policy
DHA reserves the right at any time and without notice to change this Privacy Policy simply by posting such changes on our website. Any such change will be effective immediately upon posting.
Contacting Us About Our Website
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the operattions of this website, or your dealings with our website, please contact:
Delaware Humane Association
701 A Street
Wilmington, DE 19801
(302) 571-8171 x301
development@delawarehumane.org
No Comments
Comments are closed.
Delaware Humane Association
Adopt
Available DogsAvailable CatsHow To AdoptAdoption FeesOff-Site AdoptionsSuccess Stories Back
Donate
Make a DonationCampaign For Rehoboth PawsMemorials and HonorsMajor DonorsWish ListPlanned GivingOther Ways to Help Back
Volunteer
Become a VolunteerFoster Care Program Back
Events
Upcoming Events12 Days of DHA AuctionDesigner Bag Bingo UpdateEvent Sponsorship Back
Services
Dog LicensesPet Food PantryLow Cost Spay / NeuterRent Our SpaceAnimal IntakeVaccination ClinicsOne Health DelawareDog TrainingAdopter ResourcesHelpful Links Back
About
COVID-19 UpdateFAQsWho We AreOur LeadershipDHA RehobothBy The NumbersJoin Our TeamWhat’s New! Back
× Close Panel
Due to the current pandemic, we are proceeding with all adoptions, intake and other services by appointment only.
VIEW OUR FULL COVID-19 UPDATE HERE
Our 12 Days of DHA Virtual Auction is live! Help support our animals in need while knocking out a little holiday shopping for loved ones…and yourself!
EXPLORE 12 DAYS OF DHA AUCTION HERE
×
